It's 2 a.m. What are you doing up?
(Sheldon:)Nobel Prize acceptance ceremony
streaming live from Stockholm.
Sure. Wanna see what all the scientists
are wearing this year.
(Sheldon:)Look at these men.
(Sheldon:)They've managed to win
the top science prize in the world...
(Sheldon:)...with no more understanding
of the quantum underpinnings...
(Sheldon:)...of the expansion of the early universe
than God gave a goose.
(Sheldon:)You should pay attention, Leonard.
Someday it's gonna be you up there.
(Leonard:)- Thanks.
- So, what's got you up?
(Sheldon:)Did you have a bad clam?
- I didn't have clams.
- I don't watch you 24 hours a day.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what you do.
(Leonard:)It's this Jimmy Speckerman thing.
I can't decide if I should agree...
...to see him or not. That might be
because the last time I ran into him...
(Leonard:)...he made me floss
with my own shoelaces.
(Sheldon:)Wear loafers.